<idea-plugin url="https://github.com/github-2013/intellij-awesome-console-x">
	<name>Awesome Console X</name>
	<id>awesome.console.x</id>
	<vendor email="553926121@qq.com">awesome console x productions</vendor>
	<description>
		<![CDATA[
			<p>Special thanks to anthraxx <a href="https://github.com/anthraxx/intellij-awesome-console" target="_blank">intellij-awesome-console</a> for providing the open-source code, which has enabled me to continue using such an excellent plugin.</p>
			<p />
			<p>Finally a plugin that makes links in your console and terminal at least 200% more awesome!<p/>
			<br/>
			<p>With this plugin all files and links in the console and terminal will be highlighted and can be clicked. Source code files will be opened in the IDE, other links with the default viewer/browser for this type.<p/>
			<p>Now you just need to configure your favorite Logger to include the file name (and optionally a line number) and you can instantly jump to that file that throws this stupid error.<p/>
		]]>
	</description>
	<change-notes>
		<![CDATA[
        <p>
        	<b>0.1337.27</b><br/>
        	<ul>
        		<li>Fixed Git rename format path detection with dedicated REGEX_GIT_RENAME pattern</li>
        		<li>Added specialized regex pattern to match Git rename format: path/{old => new}/file</li>
        		<li>Improved FILE_PATTERN to prioritize Git rename format matching</li>
        		<li>Fixed testGit test case failure - now correctly matches all Git rename format paths</li>
        		<li>Enhanced support for complex Git rename scenarios with spaces in arrow notation (=>)</li>
        	</ul>
        	<b>0.1337.26</b><br/>
        	<ul>
        		<li>Enhanced link filtering with new regex patterns for dots, backslashes, and letters-only matches</li>
        		<li>Refactored ignore logic: renamed isPartOfEllipsis to shouldIgnoreMatch with expanded functionality</li>
        		<li>Added intelligent filtering for sentence-ending dots, ellipsis, and backslashes</li>
        		<li>Simplified default ignore pattern to: ^node_modules/|^(?i)(test|testing|start|starting)$</li>
        		<li>Added 5 new test methods with 143 lines of test code for comprehensive validation</li>
        		<li>Improved detection accuracy: prevents "Building...", "word.", "(\)" from being misidentified as files</li>
        		<li>Better handling of punctuation in console output while maintaining valid path detection</li>
        		<li>Added support for Git rename format with directory path changes in curly braces (e.g., {old/path => new/path}/file.ts)</li>
        		<li>Enhanced REGEX_CHAR to properly handle curly braces in Git rename operations</li>
        		<li>Enabled previously commented test cases for complex Git rename scenarios with directory restructuring</li>
        	</ul>
        	<b>0.1337.25</b><br/>
        	<ul>
        		<li>Add command-line argument filtering to prevent common commands from being misidentified as files</li>
        		<li>Enhanced default ignore pattern to filter 21 common command arguments (dev, test, build, start, run, serve, watch, prod, production, development, staging, debug, release, install, update, upgrade, init, create, generate, deploy, publish, lint, format, clean)</li>
        		<li>Solve the issue where commands like "npm run dev" or "rsbuild dev" incorrectly highlight "dev" as a file link</li>
        		<li>Add comprehensive test coverage with 3 new test methods (221 lines of test code)</li>
        		<li>Test coverage includes: command argument filtering, ignore pattern toggle, and custom ignore pattern scenarios</li>
        		<li>Maintain backward compatibility with existing ignore rules (relative paths, node_modules)</li>
        		<li>Support for frontend build tools: npm, yarn, pnpm, rsbuild, vite, webpack, and more</li>
        	</ul>
			<b>0.1337.24</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Fix MSVC C++ compiler error format detection (e.g., file.cpp(42))</li>
				<li>Support parentheses format with only line number (not just line:column)</li>
				<li>Add comprehensive test cases for styled terminal paths with branch information</li>
				<li>Support detection of paths with special symbols (⚡, ±, *, etc.)</li>
				<li>Test coverage for various terminal prompt formats (parentheses, brackets)</li>
				<li>Validate path extraction from git branch indicators</li>
				<li>Support Unix-style (~/) and Windows-style paths in terminal prompts</li>
				<li>Add ANSI color preservation feature with configurable toggle in settings</li>
				<li>Support modern shell prompts (oh-my-posh, starship) with ANSI escape sequences</li>
				<li>Intelligent ANSI escape sequence preprocessing for path detection</li>
				<li>Test coverage for various ANSI color formats (RGB, 256-color, basic colors)</li>
				<li>Backward compatible: ANSI filtering disabled by default</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.23</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Add support for Rust module paths with line and column numbers</li>
				<li>Improve test coverage with 58 test cases (100% pass rate)</li>
				<li>Upgrade to IntelliJ Platform Gradle Plugin 2.2.1</li>
				<li>Compatible with IntelliJ IDEA 2024.2 and above</li>
				<li>Upgrade to Java 21 with Amazon Corretto support</li>
				<li>Debug mode toggle for development and troubleshooting</li>
				<li>Configurable line length limit (default: 1024 characters)</li>
				<li>Chunk-based processing for long lines</li>
				<li>Multi-type matching: URLs, file paths, Java classes</li>
				<li>Result limit configuration (default: 100 matches per hyperlink)</li>
				<li>Custom file pattern regex support with required groups</li>
				<li>Ignore pattern regex to exclude specific matches</li>
				<li>"Choose Target File" popup compatibility fix</li>
				<li>Non-text file types configuration</li>
				<li>Symlink resolution support</li>
				<li>ConcurrentHashMap-based file caching mechanism</li>
				<li>Thread-safe operations with ReentrantReadWriteLock</li>
				<li>VFS and DumbMode event listeners for cache updates</li>
				<li>ThreadLocal Matcher instance caching</li>
				<li>Parallel stream processing for improved performance</li>
				<li>Enhanced AwesomeLinkFilter with advanced regex patterns</li>
				<li>Improved AwesomeConsoleConfig with validation</li>
				<li>Persistent configuration storage in awesomeconsole.xml</li>
				<li>Comprehensive utility classes for file operations</li>
				<li>Project-level file iteration and caching</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.22</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>merge pull request from anthraxx/intellij-awesome-console</li>
				<li>compitable java 22</li>
				<li>require webstorm2024.3 above</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.21</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>fix some bugs</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.20</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>fix version range</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.19</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>compatible 2024.2 above</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.18</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>fix git pull new file doesn't open in edit</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.17</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>fix didn't work in new idea</li>
				<li>add junit:4.13.2 for test case</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.16</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>fix awesome console x configurable panel isn't load</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.15</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>add match to /xxx/xx/.pnpm/@xxx+xx@x.x.x_xxx-xx@x.x.x/xxx/xx.xx:x:x</li>
				<li>add match node_modules path toggle checkbox</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.14</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>add some default values for config panel</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.13</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Fix doesn't match invisible path on mac</li>
				<li>Fix config panel don't save state in persist</li>
				<li>change java sdk with 17</li>
				<li>compatible to 2023.2.6 above</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.12</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Fix jumping to wrong cursor position on folded sources</li>
				<li>Bumped minimum Java version to 11</li>
				<li>Fix crash caused by incompatible HyperlinkHandler</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.11</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Fix crash caused by concurrency issue with multiple consoles</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.10</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Added support to scroll to column numbers</li>
				<li>Improved detection of specific python traceback logs in quotes</li>
				<li>Guard regex group edge case to avoid crash</li>
				<li>Guard row and column number parsing</li>
				<li>Fixed project cache memory leak on project close</li>
				<li>Fixed support for windows paths with row:col</li>
				<li>Fixed support '@' character in paths</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.9</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Improved compatibility with IDEA 2020.2</li>
				<li>Performance improvements in terminal mode</li>
				<li>Added line and column number support for Maven</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.8</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Support for unicode path and filenames.</li>
				<li>Improved detection for various corner cases.</li>
				<li>Improved windows path detection.</li>
				<li>Fixed configuration panel.</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.7</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Improved fully qualified name detection.</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.6</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>More robust filename detection.</li>
				<li>Improved subdirectory detection.</li>
				<li>Support for arbitrary URL schemes.</li>
				<li>Support for Windows style absolute paths.</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.5</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Increased performance, especially with large projects.</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.4</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Added config to Settings -> Other Settings:</li>
				<li>Limit the matching of very long lines by a specific length. This may increase performance.</li>
				<li>Continue matching after the limit chunk by chunk, so links after the limit may also be found. This affects performance.</li>
				<li>Match URLs (file, ftp, http(s)). Unchecking may increase performance.</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.3</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Limited filter length per line.</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.2</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Support links for fully qualified names.</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337.1</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Support all IntelliJ based IDEs.</li>
			</ul>
			<b>0.1337</b><br/>
			<ul>
				<li>Initial release.</li>
			</ul>
		</p>
		]]>
	</change-notes>
	<depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
	<extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
		<consoleFilterProvider implementation="awesome.console.AwesomeLinkFilterProvider"/>
		<applicationConfigurable
			instance="awesome.console.config.AwesomeConsoleConfig"
			id="awesome.console.config.AwesomeConsoleConfig"
			displayName="Awesome Console X"
		/>
		<applicationService
			serviceImplementation="awesome.console.config.AwesomeConsoleStorage"
		/>
		<notificationGroup displayType="BALLOON" id="Awesome Console X" />
	</extensions>
</idea-plugin>
